http://www.ihhs.net/sweat-help-home/privacy-policy.html

Patients Family and Friends Donate Medical Professionals
Know SweatWhat is hyperhidrosis?Understanding SweatingTwo Types of HyperhidrosisDefining HyperhidrosisDiagnosing HyperhidrosisPublished Scientific ResearchOur News BlogKnow Sweat PodcastsYour StoriesEmployers, Family, & Friends MessageSweating Where?Get SpecificSweaty UnderarmsSweaty HandsSweaty FeetFace and HeadSweaty EverywhereOther SweatingNight SweatsBack, Groin, OtherGustatory/Frey's (Sweat & Eating)Anhidrosis (No Sweat)Bromhidrosis (Odor Issues)Chromhidrosis (Colored Sweat)Hematidrosis (Blood in Sweat)TreatmentsFor HyperhidrosisTreatment OverviewAntiperspirantsAntiperspirant BasicsTips for Best Results-OTCTips for Best Results-RxNot Just for UnderarmsConnection to Alzheimer's?Linked to Breast Cancer?Laundry SolutionsBotox® IontophoresisLasersmiraDry®Natural RemediesOral MedicationsQbrexza®Surgeries, UnderarmSurgery, ETSInsurance ToolsYour Money. Your Health.Cost of HyperhidrosisInsurance and ReimbursementLetter of Medical NecessityPreauthorization Request FormHyperhidrosis Coverage PoliciesWhen You've Been Denied CoverageBotox Insurance HelpIontophoresis Insurance HelpQbrexza Insurance HelpTake Action!Your ChecklistSubscribe to our Newsletter BlogSearch Our Clinician FinderChoose Your DoctorPrepare for Your AppointmentShop Fan Fave ProductsParticipate in Research:—Research FAQsDonate2020 Hyperhidrosis Awareness MonthAbout UsOur CredentialsAbout the International Hyperhidrosis SocietyBoard MembersStaffAdvocatesPatient-Focused Drug DevelopmentOur Support NetworkHow Corporations Can HelpSupport GuidelinesDonatePress Releases AwardsCommunity GuidelinesTerms of UseContact Us Menu
Know SweatWhat is hyperhidrosis?Understanding SweatingTwo Types of HyperhidrosisDefining HyperhidrosisDiagnosing HyperhidrosisPublished Scientific ResearchOur News BlogKnow Sweat PodcastsYour StoriesEmployers, Family, & Friends MessageSweating Where?Get SpecificSweaty UnderarmsSweaty HandsSweaty FeetFace and HeadSweaty EverywhereOther SweatingNight SweatsBack, Groin, OtherGustatory/Frey's (Sweat & Eating)Anhidrosis (No Sweat)Bromhidrosis (Odor Issues)Chromhidrosis (Colored Sweat)Hematidrosis (Blood in Sweat)TreatmentsFor HyperhidrosisTreatment OverviewAntiperspirantsAntiperspirant BasicsTips for Best Results-OTCTips for Best Results-RxNot Just for UnderarmsConnection to Alzheimer's?Linked to Breast Cancer?Laundry SolutionsBotox® IontophoresisLasersmiraDry®Natural RemediesOral MedicationsQbrexza®Surgeries, UnderarmSurgery, ETSInsurance ToolsYour Money. Your Health.Cost of HyperhidrosisInsurance and ReimbursementLetter of Medical NecessityPreauthorization Request FormHyperhidrosis Coverage PoliciesWhen You've Been Denied CoverageBotox Insurance HelpIontophoresis Insurance HelpQbrexza Insurance HelpTake Action!Your ChecklistSubscribe to our Newsletter BlogSearch Our Clinician FinderChoose Your DoctorPrepare for Your AppointmentShop Fan Fave ProductsParticipate in Research:—Research FAQsDonate2020 Hyperhidrosis Awareness MonthAbout UsOur CredentialsAbout the International Hyperhidrosis SocietyBoard MembersStaffAdvocatesPatient-Focused Drug DevelopmentOur Support NetworkHow Corporations Can HelpSupport GuidelinesDonatePress Releases AwardsCommunity GuidelinesTerms of UseContact Us
Home
About Us
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, etc
The information provided by the International Hyperhidrosis Society (“the IHHS” or “the Society”) is for informational purposes only and is not meant to be a substitute for advice provided by a physician or other qualified medical professional. You should not use the information contained herein for diagnosing a health or fitness problem or disease. You should always consult with a doctor or other healthcare professional.It is not the intention of the IHHS to provide specific medical advice, but rather to provide users with information to better understand their health and their diagnosed disorder. Specific medical advice will not be provided, and the IHHS urges you to consult with a qualified physician for diagnosis and for answers to your personal questions. The IHHS cannot answer any unsolicited e-mails requesting personal medical advice and expressly disclaims all liability for treatment, diagnosis, decisions and actions taken or made or not taken or made in reliance upon information contained in this Web site.The IHHS does not endorse or recommend any specific commercial products, processes, treatments, or services. The views and opinions of authors expressed on the IHHS Web site may not be used for advertising or product endorsement purposes, without the express written permission of the Society.COPYRIGHT All materials posted on this Web site of the International Hyperhidrosis Society (www.SweatHelp.org) are subject to copyrights owned by the International Hyperhidrosis Society (IHHS). Reproduction, retransmission or reprinting is prohibited without prior written permission from the International Hyperhidrosis Society and appropriate attribution.The International Hyperhidrosis Society names and logos and all related product and service names are trademarks, service marks or registered trademarks of their respective owners and may not be used by any other party without the express written permission of their respective owners.The International Hyperhidrosis Society (IHHS) offers educational symposia to healthcare professionals. No part of the symposia may be reproduced or recorded in any way without the express written permission from the Executive Director of the IHHS.You should assume that all contents of the International Hyperhidrosis Society Web site (hereinafter, “the Site”) are copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used except as provided herein and without the express written permission of the Society. Except as expressly provided above, nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring any license or right under any Society copyright.USER RESPONSIBILITYEach person assumes full responsibility and all risks arising from use of the Site. IN NO EVENT SHALL ANY MEMBER OF THE INTERNATIONAL HYPERHIDROSIS SOCIETY, OUR AFFILIATES AND THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, REPRESENTATIVES, AND INFORMATION PROVIDERS, AND LICENSORS AND THEIR RESPECTIVE HEIRS AND ASSIGNS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, SPECIAL (INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFIT), PUNITIVE, OR OTHER DAMAGES ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE EXISTENCE OR USE OF THE SITE, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER THE IHHS OR ANY OF THE OTHER ENTITIES OR PERSONS LISTED ABOVE HAS BEEN ADVISED AS TO THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. This includes damages to, or damages from viruses that may infect, your computer equipment. Without limiting the foregoing, everything on the Site is provided to you "AS IS," AND THE IHHS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE WITH RESPECT TO THE SITE. THE IHHS HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, CREATED BY LAW, CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. THE IHHS MAKES NO REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY THAT ACCESS TO THE SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE ON A TIMELY BASIS OR WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, OR THAT THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE SITE WILL BE TIMELY OR ERROR-FREE. Please note that some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so some of the above exclusions may not apply to you. Check your local laws for any restrictions or limitations regarding the exclusion of implied warranties.LIABILITYSo far as permitted by applicable laws, the IHHS does not accept liability for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect, or punitive loss or damage arising out of access to, use of, or inability to use this Site, or for any errors or omissions in the content thereof.LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITESThis Web site may contain links to other Web sites. The IHHS is not responsible for and does not control the contents or performance of other Web sites, and accepts no responsibility for the consequences of your use thereof.PRIVACY POLICYThe IHHS understands your concerns around personal privacy. We know that your healthcare is a very private and personal matter. Therefore, we will not collect any personal information without your express consent.Any information gathered with your consent will never be sold, traded, or given to any organization or individual outside of the Society. We will use your information only for the express purpose for which it was provided to us. When the Society receives 'personally identifiable information'--which means any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number, etc.--we may use it for reasonable business purposes, such as contacting you, via e-mail or regular mail, to provide you with information we believe may be of interest. If you e-mail us, you are voluntarily releasing information to us. Your e-mail address may be used to respond to you.From time to time, we may use "cookies," which assign a unique, random code to identify a particular computer, in order to track visitors' movements throughout the Site or otherwise enhance your visit. The cookies report this information to our servers only. The cookies do not tell us your e-mail address or anything else personal about you. In addition, we may at times aggregate the information and use it to make changes to the Site in order to improve the Site.We have implemented technology and security policies, rules, and measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss.Since we conduct research on user demographics, interests, and behaviors based upon information provided to us during use of our Web sites, we may combine your information with information collected from other individuals to produce anonymous, aggregated statistical information. Aggregated data do not include personally identifiable information. We use this demographic information, such as the percentage of male or female visitors, or the percentage of visitors within certain age brackets, to improve the content of the Site. We also may share this anonymous, aggregated information, which does not identify particular individuals or associate particular individuals with an illness or a condition, with partners or other third parties.CLICKSTREAM DATA AND IP ADDRESSESA “clickstream” or “clickstream data” reflects the path taken by a user through the Site. Most importantly, it represents the traffic pattern by which a user moves from one Web page to another. We track such information only within this site.We track and use this information to understand how our users’ habits vary in order to better personalize the content, banner ads, and promotions that you and other users will see on the Site. This data do not contain or reveal any personally identifiable information about the user.An Internet protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider (ISP) whenever you log onto the Internet. Like providers of other Internet sites, the IHHS may use IP addresses to collect aggregate and anonymous information about the number of visitors and site usage. The IHHS does reserve the right, however, to use IP addresses to identify individuals who threaten the Site, our service, or our customers.MODIFICATIONS AND TERMS OF USEThe IHHS reserves the right to modify the Terms of Use for this site at any time. Any such modification will be posted on the Site, and the continued use of the Site after any such posting shall constitute acceptance of the Terms of Use as modified.
Print
Email Sign Up for Our News BlogPage 1 of 4Please complete all required fields! Get inside intel, research results, event invites! First Name*Please type your first name. Last NamePlease type your last name. Email*Invalid email address. Year of Birth*Invalid Input
Gender*MaleFemalePlease indicate your gender. Tell us about you.*Patient or SuffererParent or FriendMedical ProfessionalMedia ProfessionalIndustry ProfessionalPlease tell us who you are in the hyperhidrosis community.
Country* United States Albania
Algeria
Angola
Argentina
Armenia
Australia
Austria
Azerbaijan
China, People's Republic of
China, Republic of (Taiwan)
Colombia
Comoros
Congo, Republic of
Costa Rica
Cote d'Ivoire
Croatia
Cuba
Cyprus
Kenya
Kiribati[6]
Korea, South
Kuwait
Kyrgyzstan
Laos
Latvia
Lebanon
Lesotho
Liberia
Zambia
ZimbabwePlease select your country where you live. Postal or Zip Code*Invalid Input
Where do you sweat excessively?*Sweaty ArmpitsSweaty FeetSweaty HandsSweaty Face and/or HeadOther AreasSweaty EverywhereI don't sweat excessivelyPlease tell us where you sweat so we can help you and others. Fight SPAM*Invalid Input
Latest Blog Posts30Nov2020 Wrap OMG Look What We Did During Hyperhidrosis Awareness Month Hyperhidrosis Awareness Month 2020 was...23NovHh HaikuThe Hyperhidrosis Haiku Podcast - Listen Today We’ve dropped a unique podcast for Hyperhidrosis...13NovMoney and Sweat$ave on Sweat Management “Flexible”, “health” or “medical” savings accounts can help you save...04NovStress SweatFeeling Stressed? Stress Sweat Can Smell Worse than "Regular" Sweat, Here's Why & How to Deal It's... Tweets by weknowsweat 4WeHelp Movers Cincinnati
Publish modules to the "offcanvas" position.
